const questions = [
  {
    index: 1,
    question: "Capital of Francea",
    answers: [
      {
        option: 1,
        item: "Paris",
      },
      { option: 2, item: "Bruscels" },
      { option: 3, item: "Asia" },
    ],
    correctAnswer: 3,
  },
  {
    index: 2,
    question: "Capital of Franceb",
    answers: [
      {
        option: 1,
        item: "Paris",
      },
      { option: 2, item: "Bruscels" },
      { option: 3, item: "Asia" },
    ],
    correctAnswer: 2,
  },
  {
    index: 3,
    question: "Capital of Francec",
    answers: [
      {
        option: 1,
        item: "Paris",
      },
      { option: 2, item: "Bruscels" },
      { option: 3, item: "Asia" },
    ],
    correctAnswer: 2,
  },
  {
    index: 4,
    question: "Capital of Franced",
    answers: [
      {
        option: 1,
        item: "Paris",
      },
      { option: 2, item: "Bruscels" },
      { option: 3, item: "Asia" },
    ],
    correctAnswer: 1,
  },
  {
    index: 5,
    question: "Capital of Francee",
    answers: [
      {
        option: 1,
        item: "Paris",
      },
      { option: 2, item: "Bruscels" },
      { option: 3, item: "Asia" },
    ],
    correctAnswer: 1,
  },
  {
    index: 6,
    question: "Capital of Francef",
    answers: [
      {
        option: 1,
        item: "Paris",
      },
      { option: 2, item: "Bruscels" },
      { option: 3, item: "Asia" },
    ],
    correctAnswer: 3,
  },
  {
    index: 7,
    question: "Capital of Franceg",
    answers: [
      {
        option: 1,
        item: "Paris",
      },
      { option: 2, item: "Bruscels" },
      { option: 3, item: "Asia" },
    ],
    correctAnswer: 2,
  },
  {
    index: 8,
    question: "Capital of Franceh",
    answers: [
      {
        option: 1,
        item: "Paris",
      },
      { option: 2, item: "Bruscels" },
      { option: 3, item: "Asia" },
    ],
    correctAnswer: 2,
  },
  {
    index: 9,
    question: "Capital of Francei",
    answers: [
      {
        option: 1,
        item: "Paris",
      },
      { option: 2, item: "Bruscels" },
      { option: 3, item: "Asia" },
    ],
    correctAnswer: 3,
  },
  {
    index: 10,
    question: "Capital of Francej",
    answers: [
      {
        option: 1,
        item: "Paris",
      },
      { option: 2, item: "Bruscels" },
      { option: 3, item: "Asia" },
    ],
    correctAnswer: 1,
  },
];
export default questions;
